# Chelsi Thomas

#### **Chelsi Thomas**

250 Covey Road Auburn, CA 95603

530.263.2714 chelsilynnthomas@gmail.com

## Introduction

I would describe myself as an overachiever with great attention to detail. I am a self motivator along with the support of my amazing husband and 2 kids, who happen to be my biggest cheerleaders. With a bachelors in Entrepreneurship I have knowledge of bits and pieces of all things business but I've found that my true passion is client experience. Nothing brings me more joy than making someone's day brighter.

# **Experience**

### Amazon Personal Shopper/ Stylist

FEBRUARY 2022-JANUARY 2023 Remote

I worked as a remote stylist for the Amazon Personal Shopper program for almost one year. My focus was to style clients based on their personal profiles, attach a personal note to each shipment explaining why I chose those pieces. I was a chat stylist so I was also responsible for chatting with customers real time to help update their profiles as well as give style advice and information about the program. I also participated in Node Creation during my time there as well as training new hires for the chat program..

## Stitch Fix/ Stylist

NOVEMBER 2015 - JULY 2020 Remote

I worked as a remote stylist for Stitch Fix for about 5 years. My focus was to style clients based on their personal profiles, attach a personal note to each shipment explaining why I chose those pieces, and reviewing my work after the client had received the Fix to see if and where I could improve.

#### Nordstrom/ Sales Associate

FEVRUARY 2014 - NOVEMBER 2015, San Diego-Roseville, CA

At Nordstrom I worked as a sales associate in the Women's department. My job focused on finding items that fit my clients' needs and at times adding accessories and shoes to complete the look. I worked closely with a team in this environment to keep a clean and friendly department where customers felt welcome.

#### **Mccalous/** Department Manager

MAY 2012- MAY 2013, Auburn, CA

I started at Mccalous as a clerk in the juniors department and was promoted to department manager after a few short months. I was responsible for merchandising the department, working with the juniors buyers to ensure we had the merchandise we needed, and managing a team of 3-4 people depending on the time of year.

**Education** 

# Sacramento State / BA Business Admin (Entrepreneurship)

MONTH 2014 - MONTH 2016, SACRAMENTO, CA

## Sierra College / AS Business Admin

MONTH 2011 - MONTH 2013, ROCKLIN, CA

Skills

Computer skills, Customer Service Experience, Management Skills, Time Management, Ability to Multitask, Great Attention to Detail, Knowledge of Personal Styling, Up to Date with Current Trends, Excellent Communcation Skills